gold-software.com 2002-12-07

# Privacy policy

**GOLD-SOFTWARE.COM: PRIVACY POLICY**

At Gold-Software Development, your security and privacy is of the utmost importance to us. We take the following steps to protect your personal information: 

* * *

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Gold-Software Development collects basic contact information when you subscribe to newsletter or fill in a contact form. This information will be used for administrative and identification purposes only and will not be shared with our partners or third parties. Personal information is stored on Gold-Software Development computers and is only accessed by authorized Gold-Software Development personnel. 

**COOKIES**

Gold-Software Development uses a cookie to store your visiting and referrer information. A cookie is a small text file, stored on your computer's hard drive, that can be read by our system when you return to our site.

**GENERAL INFORMATION**

Gold-Software Development also collects general demographic information about visitors to our site. The information we collect creates a broad picture of our population rather than focusing on any one individual. This information is used to continually refine our products and to identify the most popular areas of our site.

**ENCRYPTED CREDIT CARD PURCHASES**

If you use a credit card to purchase a Gold-Software Development product, the credit card number is encrypted as it passes over the internet. Your credit card number is not kept or recorded by Gold-Software Development or our computers - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to purchase the course. In this respect, buying a course from Gold-Software Development is similar to a credit card purchase at any store. Neither Gold-Software Development nor the store keeps your credit card number on file.

* * *

More than anything, Gold-Software Development tries to treat its customers as each one of us would like to be treated. We value our privacy and we value yours, too. It is our goal to make your experience with Gold-Software Development a safe and positive experience. 

For more information on Gold-Software Development’s privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at: [privacy@gold-software.com](mailto:privacy@gold-software.com).
